Finding Aid for Arthur J. Tuttle Papers 1849-1958
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Criminal Files
  - 1912-1923
    - Muscalino, Genevieve (Box 43)
    - Muscalino, Joseph (Box 43)
    - Myers, Joseph (Box 43)
    - N-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Neibert, Walter (Box 43)
    - Neisher, Otto (Box 43)
    - Neuman, John (Box 43)
    - Nichamin, Harry (Box 43)
      (receiving stolen property)
    - Norton, Earl J. (Box 43)
      (theft of U.S. property (gun), 17 years old)
    - Nowak, Lawrence (Box 43)
    - O-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Oprish, Samuel (Box 43)
    - Owens, Marion (Box 43)
    - P-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Palmer, Victor L. (Box 43)
    - Paratitch, Mark (Box 43)
    - Passmore, James Leslie (Box 43)
    - Piper, Irvin P. (Box 43)
    - Pluff, Fred (Box 43)
    - Powell, William (Box 43)
      (Espionage Act)
    - Powers, William G. (Box 43)
    - Quandt, Herbert (Box 43)
    - R-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Randall, Richard and Wm. Roy (Box 43)
    - Raspa, Charles & William Leffler (Box 43)
      (Espionage)
    - Ravich, John (Box 43)
    - Reese, Philip (Box 43)
    - Reetz, Fred (Box 43)
    - Rendziak, Frank (Box 43)
      (Mann Act, Congressman James M. Mead)
    - Rosen, Samuel (Box 43)
    - Rushman, Clarence (Box 43)
    - Russo, Louis (Box 43)
    - S-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Schermerhorn, Charles (Box 43)
    - Schooler, Dave (Box 43)
    - Schornack, Frank (Box 43)
    - Seamon, Sol (Box 43)
    - Seech, Michael (Box 43)
    - Seick, William (Box 43)
    - Shanley, Eugene (Box 43)
    - Sharer, Luther (Box 43)
    - Shields, Thomas (Box 43)
    - Sigel, Dr. Tobias (Box 43)
      (Anti-American sentiment)
    - Siska, Erwin (Box 43)
    - Smith, John (Box 43)
      (narcotics, Canadian citizen)
    - Snell, Oscar alias O.J. Murray (Box 43)
    - Snyder, Harry (Box 43)
    - Sperling, Paul W. (Box 43)
    - Stetson, Frank (Box 43)
    - Stein, George (Box 43)
      (fraud)
    - Stowell, William (Box 43)
    - Stopa, Anthony (Box 43)
    - Strezlecki, Joseph (Box 43)
    - Strom, Clarence (Box 43)
      (mail theft, counterfeiting money orders)
    - Sula, Joseph (Box 43)
    - Sylvester, Otto (Box 43)
    - T-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Taylor, Robert (Box 43)
    - Tessin, Glenn (Box 43)
    - Thorn, J.W. (Box 43)
    - Tomes, Russell (Box 43)
    - Toto, Frank (Box 43)
    - Trudell, Charles (Box 43)
    - Tucker, Lawrence (Box 43)
    - V-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - VanFleet, Louis (Box 43)
    - VanMeter, Edward (Box 43)
      (not given, prisoner describes in detail conditions in the Wayne Co. Jail and demands speedy trial)
    - W-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Wagner, Robert (Box 43)
    - Walker, Thomas (Box 43)
    - Waltz, Godfrey J. (Box 43)
    - Warden, Isaac (Box 43)
    - Warner, Belle (Box 43)
    - Waters, Raymond E. (Box 43)
      (mail theft, Tuttle writes letter for him to draft board to allow him to enlist)
    - Wheeler, Carson (Box 43)
    - White, William W. (Box 43)
      (habeas corpus, Judge John W. Warrington)
    - Williams, Vera (Box 43)
    - Wilmer, Frank alias Ryan (Box 43)
    - Wilson, George D. (Box 43)
      (theft from railcar (coal))
    - Wilson, Isaiah (Box 43)
      (theft from railcar (coal), Wilson was pastor of black church)
    - Windom, Leslie (Box 43)
      (impersonating federal officer)
    - Wood, Frank (Box 43)
    - Woods, Louis (Box 43)
    - Wrzesinski, Anthony (Box 43)
    - Z-Miscellaneous (Box 43)
    - Zimnicky, William (Box 43)
    - Zubich, John (Box 43)
  - 1924-1927
    (Some files contain data sheets including: name, violation, circumstances, trial or plea, date of sentence, period of sentence, institution, fine, age, previous record, some contain sheets which include citizenship status, family statistics, occupation and education, many of these sheets are contained in the "Miscellaneous" files. Pardon Attorneys Daniel M. Lyons, James A. Finch, Board of Parole officials, Heber H. Votaw, H.C. Heckman)
    - A-Miscellaneous (Box 44)
    - Abel, Philip & L.C. Borden (Box 44)
    - Alberts, William (Box 44)
    - Anderson, Henry (Box 44)
    - B-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Barron, Harvey (Box 44)
    - Beattie, James Howard (Box 44)
      (immigration, Canadian citizen)
    - Borgardt, Frederick (Box 44)
    - Berry, Mrs. Roy (Box 44)
    - Billington, Arthur (Box 44)
    - Billington, Sidney (Box 44)
    - Black, J.C. alias Earl F. Day (Box 44)
      (fraud, prisoner entered bigamous marriage with a "toe dancer" while in prison)
    - Borys, Fred (Box 44)
    - Bowerman, Wilbur (Box 44)
    - Brooks, Leon (Box 44)
    - Brown, Gordon (Box 44)
      (theft of postal funds)
    - Browne, Grant Hugh (Box 44)
      (bribery and fraud, see larger file in the Case Files series)
    - Burke, John W. (Box 44)
      (liquor, padlocking of Burke Hotel in Frederic, Mich.)
    - C-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Campbell, Marshall (Box 44)
      (theft of ammunition)
    - Cannte, James (Box 44)
    - Cardigan, Frank W. (Box 44)
      (car theft, Brothers were "leaders in this gigantic fraud of stealing, transporting and selling automobiles," Senators Henrik Shipstead, James Couzens, Congressman W. Frank James)
    - Cardigan, James A. (Box 44)
    - Caughlin, Emma (Box 44)
    - Chillicothe, Ohio (Box 44)
      (Newspaper clippings, new federal reformatory)
    - Clay, Mabel & George (Box 44)
    - Comaroni, Albert (Box 44)
    - Corbeil, Edward E. (Box 44)
      (liquor, description of attempt to defend the Detroit River from the "Mosquito Fleet" of small boat smugglers)
    - Crouch, James "Diamond Jim" (Box 44)
    - Cusmano, James (Box 44)
    - D-Miscellaneous (Box 44)
    - Davis, Claude A. (embezzlement of postal funds) (Box 44)
    - Davis, George (Box 44)
    - Day, Alonzo (Box 44)
    - Decker, Frank (Box 44)
    - Denstedt, John (Box 44)
    - Deputy Sheriff Cases (Max Leo Corrigan, William Parmenter, James Quick, Henry Rivers) (Box 44)
      (liquor, corruption, Wayne County, newspaper clippings)
    - Detroit House of Corrections (Box 44)
    - Diamond, Mrs. Earl (Box 44)
    - Doban, Thomas (Box 44)
    - Dowell, Roscoe alias Robert Arnold (Box 44)
    - E-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Ellis, James (Box 44)
    - Emonds, Alfred P. (Box 44)
    - English, Loren (Box 44)
    - F-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Ferguson, John (Box 44)
      (liquor, conspiracy, Mayor of Hamtramck case)
    - Fifer, Marvin (Box 44)
      (car theft, "in control of very big automobile stealing organization")
    - Forward, Guy (Box 44)
    - Fox, Ronal (Box 44)
    - Freimann, Andrew (Box 44)
    - Fuller, Benjamin F. alias Lancelot Race Galpin (Box 44)
      (not given, discussion of recidivism)
    - G-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Greenwalt, Paul (Box 44)
    - Grgantov, John (Box 44)
    - H-Miscellaneous (Box 44)
    - Hamtramck Conspiracy (Box 44)
    - Halpin, Tom (Box 44)
    - Henning, Adelaide alias Adeline alias Ethel Marcella (Box 44)
    - Hopper, Frank (Box 44)
    - Huebel, Rudolph (Box 44)
    - Humanski, Albert (Box 44)
    - I-Miscellaneous (Box 44)
    - Implom, Margaret alias Anna Molnar (Box 44)
    - Inman, George (Box 44)
    - J-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Jewell, Lorenzo (Box 44)
    - Johnson, Joseph (Box 44)
    - Johnston, Roy (Box 44)
    - Jucaitis, Zenon Alexander (Box 44)
      (conspiracy to sell stolen U.S. securities)
    - K-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Kalinewski, William (Box 44)
      (armed robbery of mail carrier)
    - Kapustik, Beel (Box 44)
    - Kennedy, Michael (Box 44)
    - Kirtland, Carl (Box 44)
      (mailing obscene material)
    - Kolodski, Steve (Box 44)
    - Kostanecki, John (Box 44)
      (liquor, Hamtramck conspiracy)
    - Kruzoy, Rudolph (Box 44)
    - Kuczynski, Frank (Box 44)
      (counterfeiting, newspaper clipping)
    - Kulma, Robert (Box 44)
    - L-Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - LaClair, Edward (Box 45)
    - LaFlamme, Frank (Box 45)
    - Lane, Austin (Box 45)
    - Lankenau, Carl J. (Box 45)
      (National Banking Laws, embezzlement)
    - Lankenau, Edward C. & Isabelle (Box 45)
    - Laporte, Hazen Pingree (Box 45)
    - Larkin, Henry (Box 45)
    - Leavenworth Penitentiary (Box 45)
    - Lee, Francis H. (Box 45)
    - Lieder, Sam (Box 45)
      (counterfeiting, liquor)
    - Lemons, Walter (Box 45)
    - Lobsinger, Joseph (Box 45)
    - Logan, James (Box 45)
    - Loizos, Peter (Box 45)
    - Luvisch, Isadore (Box 45)
    - Mc-Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - McGrath, Percy (Box 45)
    - McGregor, James (Box 45)
    - McGregor, John (Box 45)
    - McKinnon, Bernard G. (Box 45)
    - M-Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - Maggo, Fred (Box 45)
    - Mahrle, Clarence R. (Box 45)
      (disbarred attorney, drunkenness)
    - March, Ruth O. (Box 45)
    - Marin, Morris (Box 45)
    - Martinson, Clyde (Box 45)
      (theft of government checks)
    - Mastos, Willis (Box 45)
    - Mayer, Stanley (Box 45)
    - Mazolla, Dominic (Box 45)
    - Medsker, James (Box 45)
      (train robbery)
    - Messina, Tony (Box 45)
    - Michalski, Louis (Box 45)
    - Mierzensky, Felix (Box 45)
    - Miller, Harriet "Hattie" (Box 45)
    - Momney, Joseph (Box 45)
      (Immigration law)
    - Morse, Clarence Harvey (Box 45)
    - Mosher, Harry E. (Box 45)
    - Moyer, William (Box 45)
    - Mullen, Guy (Box 45)
      (assaulting immigration officer with dangerous weapon)
    - Munke, Albert (Box 45)
      (Immigration Law)
    - Mudloff, Mary (Box 45)
    - N-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Neef, Frederich Adoph (Box 45)
      (conspiracy to blow up Detroit Screw Works, St. Clair Tunnel, Peabody Mfg. Co. (Ontario), Canadian Pacific Railroad at Nipigon, and Windsor Armory)
    - Nelson, Clara (Box 45)
    - Nyland, Ernest (Box 45)
      (fraud in government contracts)
    - Nyquist, Sven (Box 45)
    - O-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Orban, John (Box 45)
      (maintaining a nuisance)
    - P-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Parent, Wilbrod & Adele (Box 45)
      (Immigration Law, Mann Act)
    - Pope, Leo E. (Box 45)
    - Prast, Laverne (Box 45)
    - Provo, Francis (Box 45)
    - Prudhomme, Harold (Box 45)
    - Przybylski, Leo (Box 45)
    - Pusterhofer, Louis (Box 45)
    - Q-Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - R-Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - Robinson, Clarence (Box 45)
    - Romannick, Kozni (Box 45)
    - Rosenberg, Abe (Box 45)
    - Ross, Albert (Box 45)
      (liquor, Hamtramck Conspiracy)
    - Rosseau, Frank (Box 45)
    - Rossi, Angelo (Box 45)
    - S-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Saginaw County Jail (Box 45)
    - Savage, John (Box 45)
    - Scriber, Claude S. (Box 45)
      (Accepting a bribe (customs inspector))
    - Scrypczak, Edmund A. (Box 45)
    - Sears, Paul (Box 45)
    - Sedoroak, Archep alias Archuck Swiachuk (Box 45)
      (selling stolen government bonds)
    - Sharp, Ray (Box 45)
      (armed robbery, photo-mug shots)
    - Smith, Robert E. (Box 45)
    - Snellenberger, Reuben (Box 45)
    - State Welfare Commission re: Jails (Box 45)
    - Statistics: May 1926 (Box 45)
    - Statistics: October Term 1926 (Box 45)
    - Statistics: May 1-June 30, 1927 (Box 45)
    - Statistics: July 1, 1927-June 30, 1928 (Box 45)
    - Stone, Sam (Box 45)
    - Stover, William (Box 45)
    - Symonowicz, John (Box 45)
    - Szczepanik, John (Box 45)
    - T-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Tonkin, Louis (Box 45)
    - U-Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - V-Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - W-Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - Wade, Lawrence (Box 45)
      (mailing obscene letter)
    - Wagner, Fred (Box 45)
    - Walt, George (Box 45)
    - Warren, Eric (Box 45)
    - Waterbury, Lester J. (Box 45)
      (conspiring to defraud the government)
    - Wayne County-Sheriff's Report (Box 45)
    - Weller, Elmer (Box 45)
    - Widdis, Fred G. (Box 45)
    - Wilson, Charles (Box 45)
    - Woods, Harry (Box 45)
    - XYZ-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - York, Edwards (Box 45)
    - Zakshewski, Vincent (Box 45)
  - 1927-1929
    - A-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Atlanta Penitentiary (Box 46)
    - Antonewski, Joseph & wife, Josephine (Box 46)
    - B-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Baller, Henry (Box 46)
      (Burglary of Post Office)
    - Ballos, Joe (Box 46)
    - Beck, John (Box 46)
    - Brown, Frank and Mrs. (Box 46)
    - C-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Carballo, Julian L. (Box 46)
      (forgery, Senator James Couzens)
    - Carr, John (Box 46)
    - Campanilla, Joe (Box 46)
    - Connors, George (Box 46)
    - D-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Dehmel, Carl (Box 46)
    - E-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Engleman, Walter (Box 46)
    - F-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Fleming, Donald L. (Box 46)
    - G-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Gebo, Ernest (Box 46)
    - Gilbert, Roy (Box 46)
    - Gordon, James (Box 46)
    - Griffiths, John (Box 46)
    - Grundstrom, Cora (Box 46)
    - H-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Harrington, Fred J. (Box 46)
    - Hatton, William (Box 46)
      (larceny of guns and ammunition)
    - Hull, Frank W. (Box 46)
    - Hulse, Harry (Box 46)
      (liquor, Tariff Act)
    - I-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - J-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Jantz, Philip (Box 46)
    - K-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Kaufmann, William (Box 46)
    - Klack, Walter (Box 46)
    - Kraszwska, Helen & Stanley (Box 46)
    - Klichenhoff, Frank (Box 46)
    - L-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - LaFountain, Edwin (Box 46)
    - LaMorie, Mary (Box 46)
    - Lask, Steve (Box 46)
    - Lefebre, Henry D. (Box 46)
    - Lemanski, Joe & Anna & Julius (Box 46)
    - Lewis, Alexander F. (Box 46)
    - M-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous Cases (Box 46)
    - Magas, Nick (Box 46)
    - Meyers, Louis (Box 46)
    - Miller, Arthur N. (Box 46)
    - Miller, John (Box 46)
    - Monett, Louise (Box 46)
    - N-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Nagel, William (Box 46)
    - O-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Orofino, John alias Tom Tati (Box 46)
    - P-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Penitentiaries & Reformatories (Box 46)
    - Q-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Quinlan, Frank (Box 46)
    - R-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Rodeitcher, Leo (Box 46)
    - Ritenburgh, Edward (Box 46)
    - Ruhle, Clifford C. (Luman Burch) (Box 46)
    - S-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Saginaw County Sheriff (Box 46)
    - Samson, Floyd (Box 46)
    - Sayres, William (audits) (Box 46)
    - Sharp, Homer (Box 46)
      (theft from mail)
    - Sigle, Amos James (Box 46)
    - Statistics for Fiscal Year July 1, 1928-June 30, 1929 (Box 46)
    - Stinson, Minnie (Box 46)
    - Stokolosa, Paul (Box 46)
    - T-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Thompson, George F. (Box 46)
    - Thompson, John R. (Box 46)
    - Trudo, Buck alias William Furtaw (Box 46)
    - Tucker, Charles (Box 46)
    - U-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - V-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - VanCumber, Gertrude (Box 46)
    - W-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Ward, David (Box 46)
    - Warren, Wiley (Box 46)
    - Weingarden, Harold Lloyd (Box 46)
      (National Banking Law, embezzlement)
    - White, Roy (Box 46)
    - XYZ-Miscellaneous (Box 46)
  - 1929-30
    - A-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Alfano, Nick (Box 46)
    - B-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Banks, Louise (Box 46)
    - Brenner, Charles G. (Box 46)
    - Brown, Hattie B. (Box 46)
    - Burgin, George (Box 46)
    - C-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Cohen, Abe (Box 47)
    - D-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - DeCaire, Anna (Box 47)
    - DeFore, Basil (Box 47)
    - Dodd, Hazen (Box 47)
    - Ducharme, Arthur (Box 47)
    - E-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - F-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - G-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Gamby, Oscar (Box 47)
    - Gridley, Willis Timothy (Box 47)
      (disbarred attorney, mail fraud)
    - H-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Hass, Paul Peter (Box 47)
    - Hines, Alfred J. (Box 47)
    - Hoy, Wong alias Pete Mon (Box 47)
    - I-Miscellaneous (Box 47)
    - J-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - K-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - L-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Lambrecht, Nicholas alias Richard Lambrecht (Box 47)
      (armed robbery of mail truck)
    - Lamotte, Elsie (Box 47)
    - Lown, Clara (Box 47)
    - M-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous Cases-Not regularly sentenced by AJT (Box 47)
    - N-Miscellaneous (Box 47)
    - O-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - O'Reilly, William J. (Box 47)
    - P-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Piggott, Warren (Box 47)
    - Poulakis, Constantine (Box 47)
      (liquor, Tuttle criticized procedure for obtaining endorsements for executive clemency)
    - Prisons and Penitentiaries (Box 47)
      (Detroit House of Correction declines federal prisoners)
    - R-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - S-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Sparks, Amanda (Box 47)
    - Statistics 1930 (Box 47)
    - Taratuta, Mary (Box 47)
      (liquor, mother of mentally handicapped adults)
    - Tullman, Alexander alias Jack Thomas (Box 47)
      (mail theft, British citizen)
    - T-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - V-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Van der Casteele, Selma (Box 48)
      (liquor, Belgian citizen)
    - W-Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Warner, Ralph C. (Box 48)
    - XYZ-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Yick, Lew (Box 48)
  - 1931-1941
    (Beginning in 1938 the "Miscellaneous" files contain standardized dossiers on each case entitled Report of Probation Officer (Rudolph E. Boehringer or Charles T. Hosner,) containing a data sheet, and case narrative, including the offense, the penal institution, and the family and educational status of the prisoner; the judge's letter regarding probation is attached)
    - A-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Albers, Alfred (Box 48)
    - B-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Bachelor, Phoebe (Box 48)
      (forgery, narcotics)
    - C-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Chebatoris, Anthony (Box 48)
      (bank robbery, eyewitness report of execution)
    - D-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - E-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Elore, Lee (Box 48)
      (liquor tax)
    - F-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Fischbein, Samuel alias Fishbein (Box 48)
      (perjury, Austrian citizen)
    - G-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - H-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Hall, Leonard (Box 48)
    - Hoehne, Richard B. (Box 48)
      (perjury, German citizen)
    - I-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - J-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - K-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Kruczynbski, Joseph (Box 48)
    - L-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - Lafferty, Hugh (Box 48)
    - Lockhart, William H and Gaylord Raymond McComber (Box 48)
    - Mc-Miscellaneous (Box 48)
    - M-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - N-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - O-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - Owczarzak, Theresa (Box 49)
    - P-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - Pepitone, Maltese, Accardo and Raglich (Box 49)
      (liquor, tax)
    - R-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - Reiling, Clarence (Box 49)
      (rape on federal property)
    - S-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - Sigler, Dr. Cecil M. (Box 49)
    - Statistics (Box 49)
    - T-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - Tennyson, Curtis (Box 49)
      (extortion)
    - U-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - V-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - Vermont State Prison & House of Correction (Box 49)
    - Voorheis, Byron W. (Box 49)
    - W-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - XYZ-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
  - 1941-1944
    - A-Z, 24 folders (Box 50)
      (includes individual folders for Fred L. Maurer (Mann Act) and Max Stephan (treason))
- Correspondence--Incoming personal correspondence
  The Correspondence series (22 linear feet) contain incoming correspondence of a more personal nature -- not related to his office as a federal judge. These include letters from political associates, family members, and friends and invitations to various social events.
  - 1888-1898 (Box 51)
  - 1899-1901 (Box 52)
  - 1902-September 1904 (Box 53)
  - October 1904-1906 (Box 54)
  - 1907-1909 (Box 55)
  - 1910-June 1912 (Box 56)
  - July 1912-May 1913 (Box 57)
  - June 1913-March 1914 (Box 58)
  - April 1914-1915 (Box 59)
  - 1916-1917 (Box 60)
  - 1918-June 1920 (Box 61)
  - July 1920-June, 1921 (Box 62)
  - July 1922-1923 (Box 63)
  - 1924 (Box 64)
  - 1925-March, 1927 (Box 65)
  - April 1927-June 1929 (Box 66)
  - July, 1929-1931 (Box 67)
  - 1932-1934 (Box 68)
  - 1935-June, 1937 (Box 69)
  - July 1937-1939 (Box 70)
  - 1940-June, 1942 (Box 71)
  - July 1942-1944 (Box 72)
- Letterbooks -- Outgoing correspondence, personal and professional
  The Letterbooks series (19 linear feet) contains all Tuttle's outgoing correspondence, both personal and professional, in chronological order.
  - 1897-1902 (Box 73)
  - 1902-1907 (Box 74)
  - 1906-1912 (Box 75)
  - 1911-1914 (Box 76)
  - 1914-1916 (Box 77)
  - 1916-1918 (Box 78)
  - 1918-1919 (Box 79)
  - 1919-1920 (Box 80)
  - 1920-1922 (Box 81)
  - 1922-1923 (Box 82)
  - 1923-1924 (Box 83)
  - 1925-1927 (Box 84)
  - 1927-1929 (Box 85)
  - 1929-1931 (Box 86)
  - 1931-1934 (Box 87)
  - 1934-1936 (Box 88)
  - 1936-1938 (Box 89)
  - 1938-1941 (Box 90)
  - 1941-1944 (Box 91)
- Scrapbooks
  The Scrapbooks series (10 linear feet) contains scrapbooks filled with newspaper clippings concerning Tuttle, his family, and the cases he decided.
  - 1898-1900 (Box 92)
  - 1900-1901 (Box 93)
  - 1901-1903 (Box 94)
  - 1906-1907 (Box 94)
  - 1907-1915 (Box 95)
  - 1915-1921 (Box 96)
  - 1921-1924 (Box 97)
  - 1924-1927 (Box 98)
  - 1927-1932 (Box 99)
  - 1932-1940 (Box 100)
  - 1940-1944 (Box 101)
- University of Michigan
  The University of Michigan series (3 linear feet) includes hard-covered notebooks from Tuttle's studies as an undergraduate and a law student. Also included are the Sigma Alpha Epsilon files which contain primarily incoming correspondence, 1915-1944, regarding the administration of the fraternity, including Tuttle's involvement in the government of the national organization.
  - University of Michigan Student Notebooks
    - Torts (Box 102)
    - Mechanisms of Exchange (Box 102)
    - Pedagogy (Box 102)
    - International Law: Pres. James B. Angell (Box 102)
    - History of 18th Century: Prof. Richard Hudson (Box 102)
    - American Literature Seminar (Box 102)
    - Political Econ.: Prof. Henry Carter Adams (Box 102)
    - Livy Prose: Mr. Joseph Horace Drake (Box 102)
    - Music: Prof. Albert Augustus Stanley (Box 102)
    - Chemistry: Dr. Lucius L. Van Slyke (Box 102)
    - Zoology: Prof. Joseph Beal Steere (Box 102)
    - Political Economics II: Prof. Henry Carter Adams (Box 102)
    - Teaching: B.A. Hinsdale (Box 102)
    - Chemistry Lab Notebook (Box 102)
    - Modern European History (Box 102)
    - Political Economy: Prof. F.M. Taylor (Box 102)
    - Political Economy III: Prof. Henry Carter Adams (Box 102)
    - Elocution (Box 102)
    - AJT Thesis on Michigan Homestead Law (U of M Law) 1895 (Box 102)
    - University of Michigan Student Papers 1888-1892 (Box 102)
    - History of University of Michigan Class of 1892 by Arthur J. Tuttle 1892 (Box 102)
    - U-M Grade reports, programs, etc. (Box 102)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon fraternity alumni materials
    - Chronological files 1915-1920 (Box 103)
    - Chronological files 1921-1944 (Box 104)
- Financial Materials
  The Financial matters series (1.2 linear feet) contains Tuttle's financial records, including tax returns.
  - Cash 1897-July, 1909 (Box 105)
  - Cash August 30, 1909-December, 1920 (Box 105)
  - Cash 1921-1937 (Box 105)
  - Ledger 1901-1919 (Box 105)
  - Ledger 1918-1937 (Box 105)
  - Journal 1897-1944 (Box 105)
  - Inventory Book 1927-1944 (Box 105)
  - O.V. Tuttle Estate 1937 and Detroit Bank Account 1938-1945 (Box 105)
  - Account of Grocery Purchases by Mrs. Stewart 1927-1932 (Box 105)
  - Income tax returns
    - 1913-1919 (Box 105)
    - 1931-1938 (Box 105)
    - 1939 (Box 105)
    - 1940 (Box 105)
    - 1941 (Box 105)